Guide to the Nicholas School of the Environment Records, 1916-ongoing UA.18.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA 93-107, 1940-1993
  - AA (Alumni Association), 1940-1993, 11 folders (Box 10)
    - Alumni News, vols. 1-13, 1946-1959 (Box 10)
    - Duke Digest, 1955-1958 (Box 10)
    - Bulletin of Duke University: Forestry School Newsletter, vol. 33, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Duke Alumni Newsletter: School of Forestry News, various issues, 1962-1977 (Box 10)
    - Alumni class newsletters, 1990-1993 (Box 10)
    - Letters to alumni, 1984-1991 (Box 10)
  - Brochures--Duke Forest and FES programs, 1976-1985 (Box 10)
  - Duke Forest--Urban Land Institute committee report, 1986-1988 (Box 10)
  - FES Program descriptions--orientation, Fall '83 to Fall '89, 1983-1989, 7 folders (Box 10)
  - Gelbart and Associates Fellowship, 1981 (Box 10)
  - OAS: Society of American Foresters--Accreditation and Self-Evaluation Report, 1976 (Box 10)
  - PR: Fellowship--Wilderness Society, 1989 (Box 10)
  - PR: News releases, 1986-1990, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - School newsletters, weekly, 1978-1991, 4 folders (Box 11)
  - Photographs--various class photos and negatives, 1947-1983, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Photographs--faculty, various, 1948-1956 (Box 11)
  - Photographs for Alumni News, 1954-1960 (Box 11)
  - Photographs--individual alumni, 1940-1947 (Box 11)
  - Photographs--miscellaneous old photos, 1941-1981, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Photographs--Summer Coastal Studies, 1979-1981 (Box 11)
- UA 93-108, 1934-1991
  Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, printed matter, photographs, clippings, reports, handbooks, and other materials concerning the administration of the School of Forestry. Although materials were received unarranged, the 2- and 3-letter filing codes were consistent with other accessions, so materials have been gathered by these codes and arranged in alphabetical order. The major groups of materials are as follows: BV (Board of Visitors); C (Courses); DF (Duke Forest); DU (Duke University); FES (or SFES: School of Forestry and Environmental Science); OAS (Organizations and Societies); and P (Personnel).
  - AR (Alumni Relations)--Correspondence, 1940-1963 (Box 11)
  - BV (Board of Visitors), 1962-1987, 31 folders
    - Acceptances, 1964-1965 (Box 11)
    - BOV Manual, 1981-1983 (Box 11)
    - Invitations, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Membership invitations and replies, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Original membership, 1962-1965 (Box 11)
    - Study of BOV and General Information, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
    - Meetings of the Board of Visitors, 1980-1983, Folders 1-13 of 25 (Box 11)
    - Meetings of the Board of Visitors, 1984-1987, Folders 14-25 of 25 (Box 12)
  - C (Courses)--Course data and descriptions, 1956-1980, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - DF (Duke Forest)--Duke Forest annual reports, 1986-1988, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - DF--Response to report by an ad hoc committee on the Duke Forest, 1983 (Box 12)
  - DU (Duke University), 1951-1991, 11 folders
    - Academic Priorities Committee on Graduate Education, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Building plans, 1959-1967 (Box 12)
    - Committee on Environmental Science and Policy, 1989-1991, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Committees--Long Range Planning Committee, 1959-1970 (Box 12)
    - Committees--Marine Laboratory Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Departments--Institute of Higher Learning, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
    - Departments--Marine Lab, 1970-1976 (Box 12)
    - Hotel at golf course--articles, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Information on Carl H. Stoltenberg, Forestry faculty member, 1951 (Box 12)
    - Proposals, 1960-1966 (Box 12)
  - EGD--Champion Papers, 1966 (Box 12)
  - FES/SFES (School of Forestry and Environmental Studies), 1934-1991, 84 folders
    [FERPA RESTRICTIONS NOTE: "Faculty meetings and minutes" folders below, as stamped, are restricted under FERPA.]
    - Academic plan, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Annual reports, 1937-1966, Folders 1-3 of 12 (Box 12)
    - Annual reports, 1967-1982, Folders 4-12 of 12 (Box 13)
    - Candidates for degrees, 1970-1985, 11 folders (Box 13)
    - Center for Forestry Investment, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
    - Doctor of Forestry, 1939-1952 (Box 13)
    - Employment inquiries and job market, 1968-1970 (Box 13)
    - Faculty meetings and minutes, 1958-1976, Folders 1-12 of 19 (Box 13)
      [Restricted until 2064.]
    - Faculty meetings and minutes, 1977-1989, Folders 13-19 of 19 (Box 14)
    - Faculty roster, 1930-1984 (Box 14)
    - Faculty teaching summaries, 1980-1985 (Box 14)
    - Five Year Development Plan, 1975 (Box 14)
    - Forest History Society, 1982-1984 (Box 14)
    - Forest pathology position, 1954-1961 (Box 14)
    - Forestry School statistics, 1939-1969 (Box 14)
    - Fourteen years graduate student study, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Gifts and donations, 1958-1961 (Box 14)
    - Information for executive officers' retreat, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Masters project information, 1983 (Box 14)
    - McCarthy Environmental Speakers Series, 1989 (Box 14)
    - News releases and clippings, 1934-1991, 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Notary commissions, 1942-1957 (Box 14)
    - Photographs, 1958-1985 (Box 14)
    - Planning and development--Environmental Studies, MEM degree, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Planning and development--Program in Resource Ecology and Environmental Management, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Presentation to Academic Affairs Committee of the Board of Trustees, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Program planning, 1945-1964 (Box 14)
    - Programs of study and research, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Proposals for new degrees and program structure, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Reports, 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Reports--Self-study, 1965 (Box 14)
    - Reports--Self-evaluation, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Report to Academic Affairs Committee, Duke University Trustees, 1984, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - School history, 1959-1977 (Box 14)
    - Schumacher Memorial Library, 1967-1969 (Box 14)
    - Secretaries, 1951-1963 (Box 14)
    - Short Course, Summer 1955 (Box 15)
    - Summer session correspondence, 1957-1970 (Box 15)
    - Standing committees, undated (Box 15)
    - Wet Land Drainage Project, 1953-1956 (Box 15)
    - Wetlands (Duke Wetland Center), 1989-1991 (Box 15)
  - OAS (Organizations and Societies), 1946-1987, 8 folders
    - North Carolina Board of Higher Education, 1968 (Box 15)
    - North Carolina Forestry Association--annual report, 1969 (Box 15)
    - Regional Committee on Forestry Education and Research, 1956 (Box 15)
    - SAF (Society of American Foresters) Accreditation, 1965-1987, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Southern Industrial Forestry Research Council, 1984-1986 (Box 15)
    - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company--land use agreement, 1946 (Box 15)
  - P (Personnel), 1934-1990, 29 folders
    - Adjunct Faculty, 1977-1990 (Box 15)
    - Alpert, Leo, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
    - Anderson, Roger F., 1950-1984 (Box 15)
    - Baker, Joan, 1980-1982 (Box 15)
    - Barnes, Robert, 1966-1984 (Box 15)
    - Barrick, Frank, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Binkley, Clark S., 1981-1984 (Box 15)
    - Boyd, Robert T., 1980-1983 (Box 15)
    - Briede, Jan-Willem, 1981-1983 (Box 15)
    - Chaiken, Leon E., 1970-1978 (Box 15)
    - Coile, T.S., 1949 (Box 15)
    - Condrell, William, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
    - Convery, Frank J., 1971-1982, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Davis, William C., 1981-1985 (Box 15)
    - Davison, Alexander T., 1977-1986 (Box 15)
    - Dutrow, George, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Gelbert, Daniel H., 1976-1983 (Box 15)
    - Harrar, E.S., 1966 (Box 15)
    - Hart, William--State Forest Resource Planning, 1977-1984 (Box 15)
    - Heath, Milton, 1972-1982 (Box 15)
    - Hellmers, Henry, 1968-1984 (Box 15)
    - Hyde, William F., 1978-1989 (Box 15)
    - Jayne, Benjamin, 1982-1987 (Box 15)
    - Korstian, Clarence F., 1949 (Box 15)
    - Ralston, Charles W., 1953-1983 (Box 15)
    - Schumacher, F. X., 1934-1961 (Box 15)
    - Slinn, Ronald J., 1969-1970 (Box 15)
    - Wackerman, A. E., 1938-1967 (Box 16)
  - RP (Research Proposals)--Southeastern Center for Forest Economics Research, 1981 (Box 16)
- UA 94-10, 1984-1987, 1 box
  Correspondence, budgets, memoranda, financial records, proposals, and other material concerning The Center for Forestry Investment.
  - Center for Forestry Investment--budgets, correspondence, proposals, 1984-1987, 3 folders (Box 16)
- UA 95-89, 1990-1993
  Correspondence, financial data, rosters, and other records from several conferences held at the SFES in the early 1990s. Arranged in alphabetical order by topic.
  - George Wright Society Conference, Fall 1992 (Box 16)
  - NAEP (National Association of Environmental Professionals), Spring 1993, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Southern Forest Economic Workshop Spring, April 1993, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - Southwest Forest Disease Workshop, Spring 1991, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - World Bank Conference, August 1990 (Box 16)
- UA 2011-0026, 2001-2010
  Consists entirely of promotional materials--printed materials, posters, t-shirts, and other items.
  - Promotional materials, 2001-2010, Folders 1-10 of 15 (Box 16)
  - Promotional materials, 2001-2010, Folders 11-15 of 15 (Box 19)
  - Posters, 2002-2009, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Experts guides, 2002-2008, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Posters, 2002-2008, Folder 1-6 of 7 (Box 17)
  - Posters, 2002-2008, Folder 7 of 7 (Box 18)
  - Bags, circa 2002-2008, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - T-shirts, circa 2002-2008, 2 folders (Box 18)
- UA 2012-0055, 1926-2001
  Photographs, publications, reports, VHS tapes.
  - Colloquia, seminars, symposia, 1979-1994 (Box 19)
  - Development and progress reports, 1987-1992 (Box 19)
  - Duke Forest, 1986-1990 (Box 19)
  - Intensive courses, 1978-1994, 4 folders (Box 19)
  - Newletters (various titles), 1994-1999 (Box 19)
  - Posters, circa 1980-1989 (Box 19)
  - Programs and degrees, 1979-1994 (Box 19)
  - Promotional materials by year, 1983-1995 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous promotional materials, 1984-1994, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Poster, circa 1980 (Box 18)
  - Photographs, 1926-2001
    Arranged alphabetically by topic with the exception that negatives, minimally-processed snapsnots, and oversize photographs are gathered in Boxes 26-30 at the end of the folder group.
    - Alumni, 1980-1993, 5 folders (Box 20)
    - Alumni and faculty, 1981-1992 (Box 20)
    - Darley Tract, 1986-1986 (Box 20)
    - Duke Forest--management, 1981-1990, 3 folders (Box 20)
    - Duke Forest--people, studies, and scenic, 1979-1990, 4 folders (Box 21)
    - Duke Forest--teaching, 1984-1987, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Faculty at work, 1987-1993, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Faculty--ex-faculty, undated (Box 21)
    - Faculty--head shots, 1985-1994, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Faculty--old photos, 1982-1993, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Faculty--portraits, 1938-1966, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Faculty--Stambaugh, W.J., retirement, 1993 (Box 22)
    - Forestry School--miscellaneous, undated, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - General Duke University--buildings, students, etc., 1980-1993, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Intensive courses--instructors and students, 1979-1994, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - LSRC--construction, alumni tours, 1991-1993 (Box 23)
    - Marine Lab, 1985-1995, 5 folders (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous loose photographs, 1983-1993, Folder 1 of 6 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous loose photographs, 1983-1993, Folders 2-6 of 6 (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous plant studies, 1980-1993, 5 folders (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous scenic, 1989-1993, 3 folders (Box 25)
    - People--miscellaneous, 1988, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - People--Raymond E. Sullivan, 1926-1981 (Box 25)
    - Slides--miscellaneous color slides, 1979-1989, 3 folders (Box 25)
    - Students--scholarly activities, field trips, graduation, 1980-1995, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Students--social activities, 1989-1993, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Negatives, 1979-2001, 16 folders (Box 26)
      Negatives for certain corresponding folders in Boxes 20-25 above.
    - Unarranged photographs--color snapshots, 2000-2001 and undated (Box 27-28)
      Approximately 800-1000 color prints. Most depict various social events at the NSOE.
    - Photographs--faculty, undated, 6 folders (Box 29)
    - Photographs--Duke Marine Lab, undated (Box 29)
    - Photographs--miscellaneous, undated, 7 folders (Box 30)
  - Videocassettes, 1996
    [USE RESTRICTION: Originals of videocassettes are closed. Technical Services staff must arrange to have use copy made on request. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use these materials.]
    - Demaine Vickers, various commercials, undated, VHS videocassette, 5 mins. (Box 30)
    - Duke SFES, untitled and undated, U-matic videocassette (Box 30)
    - Living on the Edge: a Consumer Guide to Buying and Owning Barrier Island Property, pre-release copy, 1996, VHS videocassette, 48 mins. (Box 30)
    - Scicom, Inc. Demo and Trash Mountain, 1996, VHS videocassette, 20 mins. (Box 30)
- Printed Materials Series, 1932-1995, 1 box
  Reports and miscellaneous publications of the School of Forestry and the NSOE from its earliest years through the mid-1990s. The materials in this series were gathered from loose materials in various accessions. Arranged alphabetically, by title.
  - Alumni News Letter, Duke Forestry School, (bound volume), 1940-1959 (Box 31)
  - Annual Report, 1977-1979 (Box 31)
  - Continuing Students, 1986 (Box 31)
  - Cooperative College Program, Advisor's Manual, 1993 (Box 31)
  - Distinguished Alumni: Forestry and Environmental Studies, v.1, 1980 (Box 31)
  - The Duke Forest, January 1980 (Box 31)
  - Environment Alumni Directory, 1994 (Box 31)
  - Environmental Considerations of the Paper Life Cycle, 1995 (Box 31)
  - Faculty Curricula Vitae, February 1987 (Box 31)
  - Hazardous Substances in North Carolina: an Analysis of Public Perceptions, circa 1982 (Box 31)
  - Integrated Case Studies in Natural Resources Analysis: Annual Reports, 1979-1981 (Box 31)
  - Interim Reaccreditation Report for the Society of American Foresters, 1987-1991 (Box 31)
  - Management of the Duke Forest: Final Draft, April 1981 (Box 31)
  - Report of the Dean of the School of Forestry, 1938-1941 (Box 31)
  - Report of the Director of the Duke Forest, 1932-1937 (Box 31)
  - Research Report for 1981-82, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Research Report for 1982-83, 1984 (Box 31)
  - The School of Forestry and Environmental Studies: Relevance, Competence, and Costs, 1980 (Box 31)
  - Self-Evaluation Report for Reaccreditation by the Society of American Foresters, 1987 (Box 31)
  - Soil and the Growth of Forests, by T. Coile, 1952 (offprint) (Box 31)
  - Taeda: The Yearbook of the School of Forestry, Duke University, 1963 (Box 31)
- UA 2014-0021, UA 2014-0029, UA 2014-0046, 1950-2014, 10 boxes
  News Clippings and Photographs
  - Clippings, 1996-2000 (Box 32)
  - Clippings, 2000 (Box 32)
  - Clippings, 2001 (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Clippings, 2001-2002 (Box 32)
  - Clippings, 2002 (4 folders) (Box 32)
  - Clippings, 2003 (6 folders) (Box 32)
  - Clippings, 2004 (7 folders) (Box 33)
  - Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 33)
  - Clippings, 2005 (8 folders) (Box 33)
  - Clippings, 2005 (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Clippings, 2006 (11 folders) (Box 34)
  - Clippings, 2006-2007 (Box 34)
  - Clippings, 2007 (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Clippings, 2007 (8 folders) (Box 35)
  - Clippings, 2008 (10 folders) (Box 35)
  - Clippings: New York Times Op-Eds, 2004-2005 (Box 36)
  - Clippings: Earth File; Radio Files, 2005 (Box 36)
  - Slides, 2000 (Box 36)
  - Slides, 2001 (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Photos: Marine Lab, circa 1950-1954 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Board of Visitors, Headshots, 1999 Oct. (Box 37)
  - Photos: Board of Visitors, Head Shots, Walter Howes, 1999 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Duke Forestry Reunion, 2000 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Field Day, 2000 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Evening with Dr. Lincoln Pratson (Houston, TX), 2000 Nov. 30 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Ansel Adams Reception (NC Museum of Art), 2000 Nov. 16 (Box 37)
  - Photos: LSRC Holiday Party, 2000 Dec. (Box 37)
  - Photos: Duke/Yale Fair (Washington, DC), 2001 Feb. (Box 37)
  - Photos: Evening with Dr. Orrin Pilkey (Seattle, WA), 2001 Jan. 25 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Marine Lab Reunion, 2001 July 20-22 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Beaufort, 2002 Aug. (Box 37)
  - Photos: Yellowstone Trip (for board members and major donors), 2000 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Graduation, 2003 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Ocean Sciences Teaching Center (OSTC)/Repass Center Groundbreaking (Marine Lab, Beaufort), 2004 Apr. 24 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Kurt F. Forestry Letter, 2004-2005 (Box 37)
  - Photos: Fossil Dig Trip (for major donors, Lewisburg, WV), 2005 2005 Oct. 21-23 (Box 38)
  - Photos: LEAF Award, Recipient: Jackson Browne (Bryan Center), 2010 Apr. 17 (5 folders) (Box 38)
  - Photos: Al Gore Lecture and Hubble 3D Screening Event (Page Auditorium - Gore, Marble Kids Museum in Raleigh - Hubble), 2010 Apr. 8 (Gore), 2010 Mar. 16 (Hubble) (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Photos: Al Gore Lecture and Hubble 3D Screening Event (Page Auditorium - Gore, Marble Kids Museum in Raleigh - Hubble), 2010 Apr. 8 (Gore), 2010 Mar. 16 (Hubble) (Box 39)
  - Fifteenth Anniversary Stanback Internship Reunion (Bryan Center), 2011 Apr. 29 (Box 39)
  - Farewell to Dean Bill Schlesinger, circa 2006 (Box 39)
  - Stanback Internship Reunion, circa 2010 (Box 39)
  - Field Days, circa 2000-2010 (Box 39)
  - Stock Photos, circa 2000 (Box 39)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 39)
  - Class Pictures, 1982-1987 (Box 40)
  - Photographs found in MLAB, 2004 spring (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Photograph: Mrs. Marsh, circa 1990s (Box 40)
  - Photograph: Dr. Orrin Pilkey, circa 1960s (Box 40)
  - Digital Photograph: Dr. Orrin Pilkey, circa 1960s; 1 file; 3 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0001)
    Scope and Contents
    Digitized photograph in JPEG format.
  - Ron Perkins Fellowship, 2000 (Box 41)
  - The Science Resource Initiative, Payette Assoc., Inc. Architects and Planners, undated (architectural documents on the Levine Science Research Center), undated (Box 41)
  - Photographs: LEAF Award to Robert Redford, 2009 (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, 2002; 39 files; approximately 20 megabytes (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0002, Box 44)
    Digital photographs in JPEG format.
- UA2018-0045: Interim Dean Vincent records
  - Educational programs, 2017; 3 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0001)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Personnel records restricted until 2087.
    Document files in MS Word format.
  - Finances, 2016-2018; 10 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0001)
    Personnel records restricted until 2088.
    Document files in MS Word and Excel, and PDF formats.
  - Meetings and events, 2017; 1 file; less than 1 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0001)
    Document file in MS Word format.
  - Personnel, 2015-2018; 51 files; approximately 15 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0001)
  - Materials related to the Board of Trustees, 2017-2018; 16 files; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0002)
    Board of Trustees records restricted until 2068.
    Document files in PDF format.
  - Boards and committees, 2016-2018; 129 files; approximately 300 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
    Administrative records restricted until 2043.
    Document files in PDF, MS Word, MS Excel, and MS PowerPoint formats.
  - Diversity and inclusion, 2016-2018; 94 files; approximately 4 gigabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
    Document files in PDF, MS Word, MS Excel, and MS PowerPoint formats. One video file in MPEG-4 format.
  - Educational programs, 2015-2018; 386 files; approximately 250 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
    Document files in PDF, MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, TXT, and CSV formats.
  - Finances, 2014-2018; 364 files; approximately 200 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
  - Meetings and events, 2016-2018; 202 files; approximately 675 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
  - Messages, letters, reports, 2016-2018; 61 files; approximatley 5 megabytes (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
    Document files in PDF and MS Word formats.
  - Miscellaneous, 2016-2018; 54 files; approximately 25 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
  - NSOE Strategic Planning, 2009-2017; 235 files; approximatley 75 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
    Administrative records restricted until 2042.
  - Other Duke schools, institutes, initiatives, centers, 2017-2018; 19 files; approximately 51 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
    Document files in PDF, MS Word, and MS PowerPoint formats.
  - Personnel, 2013-2018; 358 files; approximatley 125 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
  - Policies, 2016-2017; 78 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
    Document files in MS Word and Excel formats.
  - Research, 2017-2018; 30 files; approximatley 60 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003)
- UA2018.0076
  - Al Gore Environment And Society Lecture Event digital photographs, 2010; 254 files; approximatley 1 gigabyte. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0039, Box 44)
  - Board of Visitors Spring Meeting, 2007; 19 files; approximately 150 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0012, Box 44)
    Administrative records restricted until 2032.
    Document files in MS PowerPoint format.
  - Board of Visitors Dinner digital photographs, 2011; 34 files; approximately 100 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0033, Box 44)
  - BOV Members digital photographs, 1999; 20 files; approximatley 30 megabytes (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0032, Box 44)
    Digital photographs in TIFF format.
  - Campaign photographs, 2004-2005; 133 files; approximatley 100 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0026, Box 44)
  - Carbon and Climate presentation, 2006; 1 file; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0020, Box 44)
    Administrative records restricted until 2031.
    MS PowerPoint presentation.
  - Dianna Cohen exhibition at Von der Hayden Pavilion photographs, 2010; 77 files; approximatley 350 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0035, Box 44)
  - Endowment Wall photographs, 2005; 22 files; approximately 100 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0037, Box 44)
  - Ferguson Family Distinguished Lectureship video recording, 2013; 1 file; approximately 2 gigabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0025, Box 44)
    Video file in MPEG format.
  - Joel Dunn digital photographs, 2007; 158 files; approximatley 4 gigabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0006, Box 44)
  - K.L. Jayme Vignette photographs, 2003-2005; 47 files; approximately 25 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0027, Box 44)
  - LEAF Award Ceremony videos, 2012-2013; 3 files; approximately 6 gigabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0008 and UA18-01-0001-OP-0009, Box 44)
    Video files in MPEG format.
  - LEAF Award Digital Photographs, 2009-2011; 1100 files; approximately 6 gigabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0007, UA18-01-0001-OP-0010, UA18-01-0001-OP-0038, UA18-01-0001-OP-0040, and UA18-01-0001-OP-0042, Box 44)
  - LEAF Award Student Films, 2009; 3 files; approximately 150 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0024, Box 44)